

# **ABOUT ME**



Kelly De Gannes



krd81

## CONTACT

PHONE: 0481 143 752

EMAIL:

kelly.degannes@gmail.com

# PROGRAMMING SKILLS

Java JavaScript HTML CSS Visual Basic

### **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

Mentoring & development Strong communication Project management Collaboration Analytical

### **HOBBIES**

Travel
Tennis
Dog walking
Programming

### **REFERENCES**

Available on request

# KELLY DE GANNES

# JUNIOR PROGRAMMER

### **PROFILE**

A rewarding career in merchandise planning has provided many challenges and opportunities. I am highly adaptable having worked for multiple Australian and UK retailers. My career has introduced me to analysis and systems which has highlighted my potential in the tech sector. I am excited to learn new skills and embrace the world of software development.

### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of IT – Web Development Accelerated Coder Academy

Sep 2023 – Mar 2024

BSc Hons - Mathematics
University of Kent, UK
Oct 1999 – Jun 2002
Grade achieved: 2:2 (equivalent to credit)

#### IT COURSES

Introduction to Programming – RMIT (2020)

Grade achieved: HD

Programming I - RMIT (2020)

Grade achieved: HD

Further Programming – RMIT (2021)

Grade achieved: HD

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Connor – Retail Apparel Group: Merchandise Planner

Aug 2020 - Present

Responsible for managing stocks and budgeting sales. Participated in projects including new systems rollouts.

Tigerlily: Merchandise Planning Manager

Jul 2019 - Mar 2020

A newly created role with a primary focus on implementing a robust planning/merchandising function, whilst overseeing a team of two planners.

Big W, Woolworths Group: Senior Merchandise Planner

Sep 2017 – May 2019

Responsible for managing stocks and budgeting sales. Participated in projects including new systems rollouts.